[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Everything to do with one of my very attractive booking team, right?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Got to be genes because I don't really do anything else.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What is the secret of the Morgan Freeman age-defying process?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "You don't?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "ORGAN: Are you vain?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, I try to.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Don't you?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "You played a lady's love interest finally?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, it just -- it came my way.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "What made you crumble?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Did you like playing a romantic lead finally?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Kind of.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "So have you finally performed your first love scene?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I was -- I was stunned.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Were you excited by it?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "It was a non-scripted assault.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "So it was a non-scripted assault on your lips?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Where did it go?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Where are we going?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "You never actually got to do it?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say that.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Is it a matter of bitter personal regret now?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Have you not?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You've never had an affair with one of your actresses?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "One of the things I think is I just never need to live the part.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "How have you resisted the trap, the pleasure perhaps that many of your colleagues have fallen into?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, at the end of the day, you're going to break up --", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "There is a secret that I'll tell you after the show.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "A small-time skirt chaser?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Don't chase women.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Go on, what's the secret?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "They'll chase you.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Is that your strategy?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "It works very well.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Does it work?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Just don't do it.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "How do you make yourself known as potentially available?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "They're curious.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "And does it ever fail?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "So basically, a lifetime of non-drooling has been a successful strategy?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "You need to have a large amount of respect for ladies.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Any other tips?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "REEMAN: This has happened before.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "How are you dealing with being a single man again after a long time married?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "If you say stallion, that adds a connotation that may not go over that well on family television.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Is that how this works?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Oh, you come on late at night, don't you?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Oh, I -- I just love a house of pictures, Miss Daisy.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "ANDY, ACTRESS: What are you doing there?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, growing up, the segregation in Mississippi just sort of had us all a little upset with the situation.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Your teachers tell you, get an education and go somewhere, be something.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "What did it motivate you to try and achieve in your life?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "If you stayed there.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "In the sense that you're a young black man growing up in Mississippi at the time, your chances of getting on in life are pretty close to zero?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Made it worse.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Has Obama helped the process of eradicating racism or has it, in a strange way, made it worse?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Does it unnerve you that the Tea Party is gaining such traction?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, it just shows the weak, dark underside of America.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "REEMAN: Kind of.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Are you disappointed that Obama hasn't been more aggressive in taking them on?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Oh, surely.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "You think so?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Of course, he does.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Do you think he has it in him?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "You were protecting him?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I had my shot.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "He gets you a title fight or did he just bust you out banging your head against other people's fists until you lost your eye?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "\"Driving Miss Daisy.\"", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What was the movie before that where you felt most like this is the one, I'm going to get an Oscar for this, and didn't?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Did you get to a point when you've made all these movies and you still haven't won one, you start to think, I'm never going to win an Oscar.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Five.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "The truth.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You want the truth or you want me to make something up?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Hope.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What're you talking about?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Can you tell?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Actually, no, you know.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Did you relate to him?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Well, you have different reasons for that.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "And you did?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "REEMAN: Well, I like directors that listen to me.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I wouldn't have changed a thing in it.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "\"Shawshank Redemption\"?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "So did you finally get your way?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I had to have a battle at one point, just to say, no.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "But you had to have a battle?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Well, they -- they -- they -- all the good ones understand it.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What will directors think of what you're saying?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "REEMAN: Anything I did with Clint Eastwood.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "I asked before the break, which is the movie you would make again, not to change, but just to relive the experience for whatever reason if you had a month to live, what would it be?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "He's just great to work with.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "Well, that would be interesting.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Maybe bring your friend Clint?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "REEMAN: Well, it's just that watching this young man, this actor, make this transition from I want 10 million dollars for the rest of my life like -- let me you ask you this.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Is that -- was that painful to you?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "It's a state of mind, really, is it?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Slightly, yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Did you feel like you'd been unfairly treated?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I'm cool.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "You're what?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "But have you been able to have an ongoing relationship, a friendship?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "No, I don't want it.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Not at all?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "You don't want it?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Yes, but, you know, this -- I don't -- there were no kids involved that we have to worry about in that situation.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "I don't know, I suppose 27 years together?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Well, not really.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "So you never speak to each other at all?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "No, why would it be strange?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "If you don't have that glue, I guess there's no real need to, is there?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Do you think you'll get married again?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Let's hold the thought that you're God...", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How do you have the temerity if you don't believe in yourself?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "I'm the one, the creator of the heavens and the earth, Alpha and Omega.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Who are you?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Yes, it was fun.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Do you like playing God?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "But what I mean is that if God exists it only has to -- it can only exist in you, not outside you, right?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "If you -- when you die, you feed something that lives.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Where do you physically continue, you think?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think you know that until you get there.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "And if so, what would they be?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "What would be the biggest regret of your life?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "I'm not going to tell you that.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "What's the one thing you would change if you could go back in time?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Really bad.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "How bad is it?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "No, I didn't even know what was going on.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "I mean, in moments like that, do you go through the cliche is there life flash before you kind of thing?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "Pretty much a dead -- a dead hand, yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "So it's pretty well a dead hand, is it?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Only if I have to do something and pretend that it's not dead.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "Does that impact on your acting at all?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "Left.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Were you left or right handed?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "Well, conventional wisdom says that left-handed people are much more adaptable if they have to learn to use their right hand than right-handed people, because you live in a right-handed world.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "So how has that affected your life?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "Yes, I play golf with one hand.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 821, "question": "Can you still do that?", "qSentId": 820}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "With one hand?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 825, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 824}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "Can you really?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "In my right mind.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "Not what?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "And do you believe from your seafaring that they are more intelligent?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "That was great fun.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 884, "question": "How was that?", "qSentId": 883}, {"answer": "I'm not even tempted.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 897, "question": "Are you tempted, though, because, I mean, you've got a good voice?", "qSentId": 896}, {"answer": "If -- if he gets it together, I'm going.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 907, "question": "Are you going to do this?", "qSentId": 906}, {"answer": "No, because we haven't decided actually that we're going to do it.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 912, "question": "Have you chosen the song yet?", "qSentId": 911}, {"answer": "I don't have a favorite Sinatra song.", "docId": "111229pmt", "aSentId": 918, "question": "Well, what's your favorite Sinatra song?", "qSentId": 917}]